Guide to the Gregory E. Montes urban history and travel collection, 1798-1960.
Montes, Gregory E. urban history and travel collection
- Series III. Postcards
  - Postcards - United States
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 9 - Pennsylvania Avenue, Downtown D.C., Northwest Washington, D.C. # of packets: # of items: 66 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 10 - White House and Vicinity # of packets: # of items: 72 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: District of Columbia, Washington 11 - Northern Virginia Suburbs # of packets: # of items: 101 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Florida, Clearwater Beach, Daytona Beach, Jacksonville 1 # of packets: 11 # of items: 28 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: Florida, Clearwater Beach, Daytona Beach, Jacksonville 2 # of packets: 3 # of items: 35 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: Florida, Key West & Palm Beaches, Marineland 1 # of packets: 8 # of items: 29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: Florida, Key West & Palm Beaches, Marineland 2 # of packets: 1 # of items: 26 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - State / Region: Florida, Miami 1 # of packets: 8 # of items: 26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: Florida, Miami 2 # of packets: 9 # of items: 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: Florida, Miami 3 # of packets: 7 # of items: 10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Florida, Sarasota # of packets: 5 # of items: 20 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: Florida, Silver Springs and Tarpon Springs # of packets: 13 # of items: 40 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: Florida, St Augustine 1 # of packets: 6 # of items: 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Florida, St Augustine 2 # of packets: 9 # of items: 29 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Florida, St. Petersburg 1 # of packets: 8 # of items: 30 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Florida, St Petersburg 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 20 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: Florida, Tampa # of packets: 4 # of items: 12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: Florida, General, Flora/Fauna # of packets: 9 # of items: 9 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Florida, General, Flora/Fauna # of packets: 10 # of items: 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: Florida, General, Flora/Fauna # of packets: 9 # of items: 9 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: Florida, General, Flora/Fauna # of packets: 2 # of items: 52 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: Florida, Cape Canaveral, Ft. Myers, Pensacola # of packets: 6 # of items: 39 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: Florida, Singing Tower, Cypress Gardens, Marineland # of packets: 11 # of items: 32 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: Florida, Orlando, Ft. Lauderdale, Misc # of packets: 8 # of items: 51 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Florida, Indian River, Everglades, Tallahassee, Ocala, Lake Worth # of packets: 5 # of items: 37 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: Florida, Misc. Floridian Towns 1 # of packets: 2 # of items: 34 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - State / Region: Florida, Misc. Floridian Towns 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Florida, Misc. Floridian Scenery 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 31 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - State / Region: Florida, Misc. Floridian Scenery 2 # of packets: 6 # of items: 31 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - State / Region: Georgia, Atlanta & Stone Mountain # of packets: 14 # of items: 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - State / Region: Georgia, Savannah and Misc # of packets: 7 # of items: 26 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, Oahu: Honolulu, Waikiki;Kauai, Maui # of packets: 6 # of items: 63 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, General, Big Island # of packets: 7 # of items: 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: Hawaii, Misc. # of packets: 0 # of items: 10 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 1 # of packets: 4 # of items: 23 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 2 & IL Misc # of packets: 11 # of items: 12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 3, Evanston # of packets: 1 # of items: 56 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 4 # of packets: 0 # of items: 3 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 5 # of packets: # of items: 75 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 6 # of packets: # of items: 76 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: Illinois, Chicago 7 # of packets: # of items: 79 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Louisiana, New Orleans 1 # of packets: 9 # of items: 27 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Louisiana, New Orleans 2 # of packets: 10 # of items: 14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Louisiana, New Orleans 3, Baton Rouge # of packets: 7 # of items: 43 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: Maryland, Baltimore # of packets: # of items: 39 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Lexington & Concord & Misc # of packets: 4 # of items: 11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston # of packets: 8 # of items: 48 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston Metropolitan Region 1 # of packets: # of items: 50 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston Metropolitan Region 2 # of packets: # of items: 59 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston Metropolitan Region 3 # of packets: # of items: 59 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston 1 # of packets: # of items: 58 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston 2 # of packets: # of items: 53 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston 3 # of packets: # of items: 58 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - State / Region: Massachusetts, Boston 4 # of packets: # of items: 53 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - State / Region: Maryland, Baltimore, Annapolis, Misc. # of packets: 5 # of items: 37 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: Michigan, Detroit 1 # of packets: 6 # of items: 21 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: Michigan, Detroit 2, Mackinac Island, general # of packets: 4 # of items: 20 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: Minnesota & Wisconsin, Minnesota:St. Paul, Minneapolis & Wisconsin (1) # of packets: 7 # of items: 25 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: Mississippi, General, MS Gulf Coast 1 # of packets: 3 # of items: 19 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Mississippi, General South, MS Gulf Coast 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 5 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Nebraska, Omaha # of packets: 0 # of items: 7 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: New Mexico, Aztec, Misc # of packets: 11 # of items: 53 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - State / Region: New Mexico, Albuquerque, Santa Fe 1 # of packets: 9 # of items: 67 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: New Mexico, Albuquerque, Santa Fe 2 # of packets: 11 # of items: 11 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: Nevada, Las Vegas, Hoover Dam, Misc # of packets: 3 # of items: 27 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 1 # of packets: 8 # of items: 8 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 2 # of packets: 8 # of items: 9 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 3 # of packets: 3 # of items: 39 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 4 # of packets: 0 # of items: 35 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 5 # of packets: 0 # of items: 26 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City 6 # of packets: 0 # of items: 69 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 51 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 53 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 3 # of packets: 0 # of items: 54 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 4 # of packets: 0 # of items: 65 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 5 # of packets: 0 # of items: 57 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 6 # of packets: 0 # of items: 64 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: New York, New York City Metropolitan Region 7 # of packets: 0 # of items: 56 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: New York, Ithaca, Watkins Glen, Long Island # of packets: 1 # of items: 37 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: New Jersey, Atlantic City, Newark, Asbury, Misc # of packets: 7 # of items: 67 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Oregon, Portland, Columbia River Highway # of packets: 9 # of items: 14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - State / Region: Oregon, Portland, Mt. Hood, Columbia River Highway Region 1 # of packets: # of items: 81 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Oregon, Portland, Mt. Hood, Columbia River Highway Region 2 # of packets: # of items: 54 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia # of packets: 6 # of items: 36 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Ohio, Philadelphia 2, Poconos, Pittsburgh # of packets: 6 # of items: 36 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia 1 # of packets: # of items: 61 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: Pennsylvania, Philadelphia 2 # of packets: # of items: 65 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: North and South Carolina, General # of packets: 9 # of items: 34 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - State / Region: South Carolina, Charleston # of packets: 7 # of items: 9 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - State / Region: South Carolina, Myrtle Beach, Charleston # of packets: 2 # of items: 30 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - State / Region: Texas, Austin, Corpus Christi, El Paso # of packets: 8 # of items: 21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - State / Region: Texas, Galveston, Port Arthur, Misc. 1 # of packets: 5 # of items: 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - State / Region: Texas, Galveston, Port Arthur, Misc. 2 # of packets: 10 # of items: 32 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - State / Region: Texas, San Antonio 1 # of packets: 8 # of items: 9 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - State / Region: Texas, San Antonio 2 # of packets: 5 # of items: 28 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Virginia, Norfolk, Old Point comfort, Arlington, VA Beach, Misc. # of packets: 2 # of items: 42 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - State / Region: Virginia, Mt. Vernon, Williamsburg # of packets: 4 # of items: 30 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - State / Region: Washington, Seattle # of packets: 9 # of items: 31 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - State / Region: Washington, Spokane, Puget Sound & Misc # of packets: 11 # of items: 41 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Postcards - Non-United States
    - World, General
      - Country / Region: World-wide, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 5 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Country / Region: Unknown, non-United States territories # of packets: 1 # of items: 4 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Africa
      - Country / Region: General, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 2747 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region: North Africa, Algeria, Carthage, Tunisia, Morocco, Alger # of packets: 1 # of items: 38 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - North African Cities - Casablanca to Cairo - and Jerusalem: # of packets: # of items: 92 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Asia
      - Country / Region: East Asia, China, Macao, Korea, Vietnam, Indonesia, Malaysia, Burma, Cambodia (1) # of packets: 2 # of items: 37 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Country / Region: East Asia, Hong Kong # of packets: 0 # of items: 43 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Country / Region: East Asia-Japan, Osaka, Tokyo, Kyoto # of packets: 1 # of items: 45 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Country / Region: Egypt, Iran, Syria, Lebanon, Cairo, Philde, Afghanistan,Jordan, Iran, Demascus(2),Lebanon(1) # of packets: 1 # of items: 31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Country / Region: Israel, Jerusalem, misc # of packets: 1 # of items: 77 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Country / Region: South-East Asia, Singapore, Phillipines, Java (1), Bali (1) # of packets: 1 # of items: 27 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Country / Region: South Asia - India, Delhi/Agra, Misc. # of packets: 3 # of items: 26 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Country / Region: South Asia- India, Sri Lanka, Bombay, Kashmir, Sri Lanka (1) # of packets: 0 # of items: 30 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Country / Region: South Asia -Thailand, Bangkok, misc # of packets: 3 # of items: 23 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Australia / Oceania
      - Country / Region: Australia, Misc # of packets: 3 # of items: 8 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Country / Region: New Zealand, Misc # of packets: 1 # of items: 50 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Country / Region: Pacific Islands, Fiji, Samoa, Tahiti, Bora Bora # of packets: 5 # of items: 8 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Europe
      - Country / Region: Misc: Italy, Denmark, Misc: Rome, Copenhagen # of packets: 3 # of items: 82 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Country / Region: Austria, Vienna # of packets: 1 # of items: 56 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Country / Region: Belgium, Brussels, Misc # of packets: 1 # of items: 59 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: Eastern and Central Europe, Prague, Dubrovnik, Russia, Budapest, Croatia # of packets: 1 # of items: 64 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: France, Avignon & Versailles # of packets: 0 # of items: 89 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: France, Paris 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 81 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: France, Paris 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 103 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: France, Paris 3 # of packets: 0 # of items: 54 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Country / Region: France, Paris - Bibliotheque Nationale, Palais de Justice - Arles # of packets: 2 # of items: 55 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Country / Region: France, Marseille, Carcassone, Nimes, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 64 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: France/Monaco, Monaco, Nice, Provence, Cannes # of packets: 0 # of items: 61 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region: France/Italy (Riviera), Menton, F Riviera, Corsica # of packets: 0 # of items: 52 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: Germany, Hamburg, Bremen, Munich, # of packets: 0 # of items: 65 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: Germany, Cologne, Dresden, Frankfurt, Leipzig, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 83 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Country / Region: Germany, Berlin, Potsdam # of packets: 1 # of items: 102 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Country / Region: Denmark, Copenhagen, etc. 2 # of packets: 1 # of items: 10 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: Greece, Athens, Corfu, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 47 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Naples, Pisa, Misc. # of packets: 0 # of items: 93 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Rome 1 # of packets: 1 # of items: 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Rome 2 # of packets: 1 # of items: 60 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Venice, Palermo, Pompei, Vatican # of packets: 1 # of items: 90 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Florence, Milan, Capri # of packets: 0 # of items: 75 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Lago di Como, Genova, Sorrento, Lugano, Amalfi, Siracusa, Lago di Maggiore # of packets: 0 # of items: 68 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: Italy, San Remo, Sicily, Assissi, Trieste, Tivoli, Ravello, Riviera, Misc # of packets: 1 # of items: 81 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: Italy, Mediterranean, Misc # of packets: 2 # of items: 30 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: Malta,Cypress, Malta,Cypress # of packets: 2 # of items: 29 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Country / Region: Netherlands, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 49 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Country / Region: Netherlands, Amsterdam # of packets: 0 # of items: 16 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Country / Region: Portugal, Lisbon, Misc # of packets: 1 # of items: 34 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Country / Region: Portugal, Lisbon 2 # of packets: 3 # of items: 30 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: Scandinavia, Copenhagen, Stockholm, Finland(1), Oslo (2) # of packets: 0 # of items: 83 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Country / Region: Scotland, Ireland, Edinburgh, Glasgow, Dublin # of packets: 3 # of items: 36 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: Scotland, Edinburgh # of packets: 1 # of items: (Box 18)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Madrid, Granada 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 67 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Madrid, Granada, Majorca, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 35 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Madrid, Granada 2 # of packets: 4 # of items: 50 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Madrid, Grenada 3 # of packets: 2 # of items: 20 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Seville, Madrid, Grenada 4 # of packets: 1 # of items: 10 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: Spain, Toledo # of packets: 3 # of items: 60 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Country / Region: Switzerland, Zurich, Genoa, Montreux # of packets: 0 # of items: 75 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Country / Region: Turkey, Constantinople/Istanbul 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 36 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: Turkey, Constantinople/Istanbul 2 # of packets: 2 # of items: 24 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, Gibraltar # of packets: 0 # of items: 13 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London 1 # of packets: 0 # of items: 51 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London 2 # of packets: 0 # of items: 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London 3 # of packets: 0 # of items: 51 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: United Kingdom, London 4 # of packets: 1 # of items: 59 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - North America
      - Country / Region: Bermuda, Bermuda # of packets: 4 # of items: 15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: Bermuda, Bermuda # of packets: 0 # of items: 1 (Box 18)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Montreal 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 27 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Montreal 2 # of packets: 9 # of items: 9 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Montreal 3 # of packets: 3 # of items: 19 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Montreal 4 # of packets: 7 # of items: 27 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region:Canada, Montreal 5 # of packets: 1 # of items: (Box 18)
        Expo 67
      - Country / Region: Canada, Quebec City # of packets: 7 # of items: 23 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Quebec: St. Anne de Beaupre, misc. 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 25 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Quebec: misc. 2 # of packets: 21 # of items: 40 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Ottowa & Ontario 1 # of packets: 6 # of items: 36 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Ottowa & Ontario 2 # of packets: 4 # of items: 5 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Toronto 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 7 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Toronto 2 # of packets: 3 # of items: 22 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Toronto 3 # of packets: 3 # of items: 11 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Vancouver 1 # of packets: 3 # of items: 29 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Vancouver 2 # of packets: 2 # of items: 14 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Victoria 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 43 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Victoria 2 # of packets: 2 # of items: 32 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: Canada, Misc # of packets: 0 # of items: 11 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Country / Region: Caribbean Islands, Jamaica, Bahamas, Haiti, Dominican Republic # of packets: 3 # of items: 27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Country / Region: Cuba, Cuba # of packets: 3 # of items: 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Country / Region: Guatemala,Panama, Costa Rica, Ecuador, Chile Misc # of packets: 7 # of items: 12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Country / Region: Lesser Antilles, Grenada,St. Maarten, Aruba, Curacao,Martinique, Trinidad &Tobago, Barbados, Virgin Islands # of packets: 6 # of items: 36 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Acapulco, Oaxaca, Taxco # of packets: 8 # of items: 20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Mazatlán # of packets: 1 # of items: 15 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Tijuana # of packets: 5 # of items: 9 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Misc 1 # of packets: 7 # of items: 28 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Misc 2 # of packets: 8 # of items: 30 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Misc 3 # of packets: 1 # of items: 10 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Misc 4 # of packets: 0 # of items: 7 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Country / Region: Mexico, Puerto Vallarta, Tijuana # of packets: 3 # of items: (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Country / Region: Puerto Rico, Puerto Rico # of packets: 7 # of items: 20 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - South America
      - Country / Region: Brazil, Argentina,Colombia, Rio de Janiero, Buenos Aires # of packets: 3 # of items: 24 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Series IV. Additional Items, Miscellaneous, Ephemera Posters, Artwork
  - Handwritten partial inventory from Montes (Box 20)
    Includes extensive notes on the acquisition and importance of some if the items, particularly the artwork.
  - Country / Region: Brazil, Rio de Janeiro "Ausreise nach Brasilien, Der braislianische Dampfer Raul Soares" Scrapbook of photographs in German from the 1930s showing a German family in Brazil, shows many areas., 8035 Bd. Ms. 2
  - Misc. Photos, Stamps, Small Postcard Booklets # of packets: 42 # of items: 55 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Country / Region :United States General Matchbook Covers # of packets: 3 # of items: 3 (Box 17, Folder 9-11)
  - Country / Region: South America Pictorial South America magazine (Box 20)
    Includes Buenos Aires Argentina, Rio de Janeiro and Sao Paulo Brazil and others.
  - Country / Region: United States General Four military aviation prints. T-39 Sabreliner at Los Angeles, USAF Minuteman ICBM, 2 of a NASA Saturn V at Kennedy Space Center Florida. (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego The Disinterred Agent poster. Aposcar Guevara Cruz, shows the Coronado Bridge. (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego Bario Block Party poster (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, Newport Beach "Newport Beach Harbor" painting by David Goff (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego "30th and Juniper" painting by Judith D'Agostino (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego "Cityscape" print signed by the artist Christopher Pantaleoni (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: Hawaii "Voyage" print signed to Montes by the artist Steve Matson (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California? Signed print by Jon Ascher for the graphic novel Neil. Shows a skyline at night with two figures in the foreground, possibly San Francisco. (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: Mexico City, San Diego "A photo series documenting street musicians from various cities around the world." (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: New York, Coney Island 16 photos, 1940-1950. (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: California, San Diego Photo of Turf Supper Club, Pacific Beach Pier, postcards for "Reappropriation of Assets", "Blight Elimination Plan", "Reactive vs Proactive", activist photos of "America's Finest Library!", "Public Restrooms: Smart Corner", "Who is this for?", "Juego Aqui Mañana", "Home". (Box 20)
  - Country / Region: Canada Canada 125 newspaper, volume 1, number 3, July 1992 (Box 20)